NGUYEN XUAN TRUONG

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

Link online portfolio

P 0988597698

akita141188@gmail.com



L Cau Giay - HaNoi

B November 14, 1988

OBJECTIVE

First goal: spending next 5 years to accelerate my knowledge in every aspect of software development and sharpen my technical skills to create awesome Webs/Apps that customers love to use.

Second goal: becoming a senior fullstack developer. Dedicate my ability and creativity to a professional organization.

EXPERIENCES SUMMARY

2012 - 2013 Work at KTM Company as Technical staff

2013 – 2023 Work at HaNoi Sewerage & Drainage company limited as Drainage system manager

2023 - 2024 Work at INVIV Cloud Technology Joint Stock Company as interning FullStack Developer

Three key roles in previous positions:

- System management
- Research, propose, report
- Advise and solve problems

MY DEMONSTRATING PROJECTS

- SmartPhone Web1 (100% NodeJs)
- 2. Folding card game -JS vanilla
- 3. Todo site JS vanilla
- 4. E-commerce site 1
- 5. SmartPhone webs 2 (Fe: ReactJs; Be: NodeJs)
- 6. E-commerce site 2

EDUCATION

University: Hanoi University

of Mining and Geology

Major: Information Technology

Degree: Engineer

P. LANGUAGE / FRAME WORK

- JS / NODEJS / REACTJS
- HTML / CSS / BOOTSTRAP
- **JQUERRY / EXPRESS**
- **MONGODB**

RELEVANT I.T KNOWLEDGE

- **GIT / GITHUB**
- MICROSERVICE / MVC
- **RESTFUL API**
- **DOCKER**

NON - IT SKILLS

- **TEAM MANAGEMENT**
- **RESEARCH & REPORT**
- **CRITICAL THINKING**
- **SUGGESTIONS & ADVISORY**
- **COMMUNICATION SKILLS**